http://www.autotask.com/privacy-policy

UNIFIED SOLUTIONS
Learn how our unified solutions provide improved efficiency, service delivery and business insights.
LEARN MORE
PSA: IT Business Management
EditionsIntegrationsAdd Ons
Datto RMMEB: Endpoint BackupWP: File Sync & ShareCSP: Microsoft Cloud Services
Request Demo
Request A Free DemoSee Autotask in action. Ask questions. And more. It all starts with your personalized demo.
Tell me more about*
Unified Platform (PSA+RMM)
Professional Services Automation (PSA)
Remote Monitoring and Management (RMM)
FSS / Autotask Workplace (AWP)
Endpoint Backup (AEB)
Business Continuity and Disaster Recovery (BCDR)
Sorry, but we could not confirm your company name - please complete these additional fields
Europa Island
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Heard and McDonald Islands
Holy See (Vatican City)
Vietnam
Virgin Islands (British)
Virgin Islands (U.S.)
100+
YES, I WOULD LIKE TO RECEIVE MORE INFORMATION ABOUT YOUR PRODUCTS, OFFERS, AND EVENTS. I UNDERSTAND I CAN UNSUBSCRIBE AT ANY TIME.WHEN YOU PROVIDE THE INFORMATION ABOVE, WE WILL USE IT TO PROCESS YOUR REQUEST AS DESCRIBED IN OUR MARKETING PRIVACY POLICY.
We are sorry, but we cannot process your request right now, please try again later. Thank you!
SUBMIT
SUBMIT
NO, THANKS
CLOSE FORM
YES, I WOULD LIKE TO RECEIVE MORE INFORMATION ABOUT YOUR PRODUCTS, OFFERS, AND EVENTS. I UNDERSTAND I CAN UNSUBSCRIBE AT ANY TIME.WHEN YOU PROVIDE THE INFORMATION ABOVE, WE WILL USE IT TO PROCESS YOUR REQUEST AS DESCRIBED IN OUR MARKETING PRIVACY POLICY.
SUBMIT
Request Quote
Request Quote
Request A Free QuoteSee Autotask in action. Ask questions. And more. It all starts with your personalized demo.
Primary Business*
Consulting or Professional Services
Enterprise IT/Internal Help Desk/Corporate IT Support
Independent Software Vendor (ISV) or Software Company
IT Service Provider/MSP/VAR
Managed Print/Office Technology/Office Equipment/Copiers
Other
Requested Action*
I'd like a demo
I'd like a quote
Tell me more about*
Unified Platform (PSA+RMM)
Professional Services Automation (PSA)
Remote Monitoring and Management (RMM)
FSS / Autotask Workplace (AWP)
Endpoint Backup (AEB)
Business Continuity and Disaster Recovery (BCDR)
Sorry, but we could not confirm your company name - please complete these additional fields
Country*
United States
Canada
United Kingdom
Afghanistan
Akrotiri
Albania
Algeria
Europa Island
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Faroe Islands
Fiji
Finland
France
French Guiana
French Polynesia
French Southern and Antarctic Lands
Gabon
Heard and McDonald Islands
Holy See (Vatican City)
Honduras
Hong Kong
Hungary
Iceland
India
Indonesia
Iran
Iraq
Vietnam
Virgin Islands (British)
Virgin Islands (U.S.)
Wake Island
Wallis and Futuna Islands
West Bank
Western Sahara
Yemen
Zambia
Zimbabwe
State*
100+
YES, I WOULD LIKE TO RECEIVE MORE INFORMATION ABOUT YOUR PRODUCTS, OFFERS, AND EVENTS. I UNDERSTAND I CAN UNSUBSCRIBE AT ANY TIME.WHEN YOU PROVIDE THE INFORMATION ABOVE, WE WILL USE IT TO PROCESS YOUR REQUEST AS DESCRIBED IN OUR MARKETING PRIVACY POLICY.
We are sorry, but we cannot process your request right now, please try again later. Thank you!
SUBMIT
SUBMIT
NO, THANKS
CLOSE FORM
YES, I WOULD LIKE TO RECEIVE MORE INFORMATION ABOUT YOUR PRODUCTS, OFFERS, AND EVENTS. I UNDERSTAND I CAN UNSUBSCRIBE AT ANY TIME.WHEN YOU PROVIDE THE INFORMATION ABOVE, WE WILL USE IT TO PROCESS YOUR REQUEST AS DESCRIBED IN OUR MARKETING PRIVACY POLICY.
SUBMIT
PRIVACY POLICY
Autotask is greatly sensitive to the confidentiality of your information and believes the protection of your confidentiality to be one of Autotask's significant responsibilities. As a result of Autotask's obligation to your privacy and confidentiality, Autotask has adopted the following Privacy Policy, which is applicable to all information you provide during your visits to the site:
Acquisition of Information
Autotask does not acquire any more information about you than is required by law or is otherwise necessary to provide a high level of service efficiently and securely.
Autotask Employees and Privacy
Autotask trains all Autotask employees about the importance of privacy. Autotask gives access to your information only to those employees who require it to perform their jobs.
Security Measures
Autotask makes access to confidentially sensitive information subject to rigorous procedural and technological controls, consistent with legal requirements and the demands of customer service.
Disclosure to Third Parties
It is Autotask's policy to never provide your information to third parties without your express permission or if such disclosure is necessary to process transactions or provide services which you have requested. The only exception to this policy is if Autotask is compelled to do so by an appropriately empowered governmental authority.
Privacy and Autotask Business Partners
When Autotask makes the Autotask technology or services available to business partners, Autotask will not share with them any more information than is necessary to perform the transaction you have requested. In addition, Autotask only does business with partners who agree to respect this Privacy Policy and will make every reasonable effort to assure, by contract or otherwise, that these third parties use our information, technology and services in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.
Personal Information
The Site may require visitors (general visitors to the Site) and customers (visitors with passwords that allow them to go to the password-restricted areas of the Site) to provide contact information (for example, name and e-mail address), unique identifiers (for example, employee ID number for customers), demographic information (for example, zip code and age) and financial information (for example account or credit card numbers for purchases). Autotask uses your contact information to create access to products and services on the Site, and to send you information about Autotask. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. Financial information that is collected is used to check your qualifications and bill either you or your company for products and services, as applicable. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. Autotask uses this data to tailor your experience to the Site, showing you content Autotask believes might interest you, and displaying the content according to your preferences.
Corporate Data
Protecting the privacy of a customer's personal information is a top priority; however, Autotask takes the protection of each customer's corporate data and confidentiality to be one of Autotask's most significant responsibilities. Autotask uses diligent efforts to ensure each customer's data integrity is limited to the company for which that customer works or has authorization to access by using a company-specific password, and that such company's data is not violated or accessed by unauthorized persons.
Nature of Information Acquired
The personally identifiable information Autotask acquires in processing payment transactions varies according to the nature of the transaction and the way in which merchants or financial institutions are using Autotask's payment services. More often, it may include the amount of the transaction, and your name, credit card number and expiration date, checking account number, billing address, and shipping address.
Information/Data Center Security
Autotask stores transaction information on secure computers located in a locked data center. Only a small number of Autotask employees involved in the management of the data center have physical access to these computers. Where possible, Autotask encrypts information stored on Autotask computers as a further measure of protection. Autotask uses high industry standards in the acquisition and deployment of firewalls and other security technology to prevent Autotask computers from being accessed by unauthorized persons.
Use of Cookies
A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a Web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. At some e-commerce sites, it functions as your identification card, recording your passwords, purchases, and preferences. But, at Autotask, session-based cookies are used only as described below. In order to enable our authorized users to authenticate to Autotask's application services only once per session, we use "cookies" to identify the user to multiple events. When a user logs into an application, their username, unique session identifier number, and other session data are captured in the cookie file, thus enabling the user to traverse through the screens of the application without authenticating at each new screen. Autotask Cookies are terminated at the end of the session, or after 90 minutes of idle time.
No other information is captured in the cookie file, nor is any information permanently transferred to the user's system.
Access by Our Employees
Autotask customer service representatives have access to some transaction information in order to respond to your questions. Autotask limits that access to the minimum information required in order to provide prompt, high quality service. For example, these Autotask employees do not generally have access to complete credit card numbers. In general, Autotask employees who do have access to Autotask databases have undergone background checks and generally only retrieve data for supporting Autotask customers' data or individual transactions, and not about individual customers.
Provision of Information to Others
To perform the Autotask services, Autotask must, of course, pass information about transactions to payment card processors and banks. From time to time Autotask may also provide third parties with aggregate information that is not linked to you or any other particular individual. Autotask does not provide to any third party your name and e-mail address, or the names and e-mail addresses of other Autotask customers.
Questions:
If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please send e-mail to privacy@datto.com
